There are barbs on the wheel of the lockbox
자물쇠 상자 바퀴에 가시가 있습니다.
Notify the Identification Department
식별 부서에 통보
Come and check it out
와서 확인해 보세요.
Is there any poison on it?
거기에 독이 있나요?
yes
예
How can one's conscience find out?
사람의 양심이 어떻게 알 수 있습니까?
Here comes a gift for me
여기 나를 위한 선물이 왔어요
Just pick
그냥 골라
Which one do you like, I’ll give you one
어느 쪽이 마음에 드시나요? 하나 드릴께요
cool
시원한
good
좋은
This is for you
이건 널위한거야
Suddenly he was so nice to me
갑자기 그 사람이 나한테 너무 친절하게 대해줬어
There must be a conspiracy
음모가 있는 게 틀림없어
No conspiracy
음모 없음
That's what I plan to do
그게 내가 할 계획이야
to my life
내 인생에
Re-plan
재계획
you won't want
당신은 원하지 않을 것입니다
Marry that girl
그 여자랑 결혼해
what did you say
뭐라고 하셨나요
Do you want it or not?
당신은 그것을 원합니까, 아니면 원하지 않습니까?
Don't let me go to the market and sell everything
시장에 가서 다 팔게 두지 마세요
Of course I want it
물론 나는 그것을 원한다
Buy one hand and sell it immediately at a high price
한 손에 사서 바로 높은 가격에 팔아요
so
그래서
I can't sell you the original price either
나도 원래 가격으로 팔 수 없어
Make a price
가격을 책정하세요
So anxious
너무 불안해
50% off the original price and transfer immediately
원래 가격의 50% 할인 및 즉시 양도 가능
Extremely anxious
매우 불안함
make a deal
거래를하다
You must be in trouble
당신은 곤경에 처해 있어야합니다
Otherwise, it would be impossible to sell equipment
그렇지 않으면 장비를 판매할 수 없습니다.
But if you don't want to say it
하지만 말하고 싶지 않다면
I can't help you much
나는 당신을 많이 도울 수 없습니다
These props
이 소품들
Someday you want to take it back
언젠가는 다시 가져가고 싶겠지
I'll redeem it for you at the purchase price
구매 가격으로 교환해 드리겠습니다.
floret
작은 꽃
you are so good to me
당신은 나에게 정말 좋은 사람입니다
I do not even know
내가 알지도 못하는
How should I repay you?
어떻게 갚아야 할까요?
I don't need it
필요없어
Let me give you a piece of advice
조언을 하나 하자면
if someone invites you
누군가 당신을 초대한다면
Participate in offline tasks
오프라인 작업에 참여
Don't answer it
대답하지 마세요
Remember
기억하다
Why
왜
Because that's a trap
그게 함정이니까
Will make you bankrupt
당신을 파산하게 만들 것이다
Look at what I have now
지금 내가 가지고 있는 것을 보세요.
It's all given to you
다 너한테 주어진 거야
You don’t want it to be like this, right?
당신은 이렇게 되는 걸 원하지 않죠?
Don't want to at all
전혀 원하지 않는다
So be sure to remember
그러니 꼭 기억하세요
Never disconnect tasks
작업 연결을 끊지 마세요
understand
이해하다
good
좋은
meet again
다시 만나다
It’s easy for me to feel like this
이런 느낌이 들기 쉽죠
you are following me
당신은 나를 따라오고 있습니다
No
아니요
This bar is owned by my friend
이 바는 내 친구 소유입니다
Nothing
아무것도 아님
I'll stay here
나는 여기에 머물 것이다
Yeah
응
Mainly last time we met
주로 지난번에 만났을 때
I didn’t get to chat with you more.
나는 당신과 더 이상 이야기를 나누지 못했습니다.
How have you been these past two years?
지난 2년 동안 어떻게 지내셨나요?
good
좋은
This bar is good
이 바는 좋은데
do you come here often
너는 여기에 자주 오니
Occasionally
가끔
Do you work nearby?
근처에서 일하시나요?
Internet company next door
옆집 인터넷 회사
That boy last time
저번에 그 아이
He's a colleague from your company, right?
그 사람은 너희 회사 동료지, 그렇지?
You have too many questions, right?
질문이 너무 많죠?
Are you still playing that game?
아직도 그 게임을 하고 있나요?
No more playing
더 이상 놀지 마세요
Just don't play
그냥 놀지 마세요
game life days
게임 생활 일
When will it be the first time?
언제 처음이 될까요?
Just don't play
그냥 놀지 마세요
Actually, it happened before
사실 예전에도 그런 일이 있었어요
I'm here to drink
나는 술을 마시러 왔습니다
I don’t want to mention other things
다른 건 언급하고 싶지 않아요
What if you want to drink
마시고 싶으면 어떡하지?
Just a few drinks between the two of us
우리 둘이서 술 몇 잔만
other things
다른 것들
Just stop talking, okay?
그만 얘기해, 알았지?
Jamray
잠레이
Bring me my bottle of wine
내 와인 한 병을 가져와
Actually what do you have
사실 당신은 무엇을 가지고 있습니까?
Unhappy incident
불행한 사건
You can really tell me
정말 말해도 돼
Because we have
왜냐하면 우리는
Haven’t seen each other for so many years
너무 오랫동안 서로를 보지 못했어요
I don't know your life
나는 당신의 인생을 모른다
He can be considered an outsider.
그는 아웃사이더로 간주될 수 있다.
Is it an emotional thing?
감정적인 일인가요?
You seem to care about my affairs
당신은 내 일에 관심이 있는 것 같아요
actually
실제로
After returning from the United States
미국에서 돌아온 후
I just realized that there are many things
정말 많은 일들이 있다는 걸 이제서야 깨달았어요
I can't let go
난 놓을 수 없어
Yeah
응
Then I'm definitely not among them
그럼 난 분명 그들 중에 없을 거야
you said
당신은 말했다
You don’t want to mention the past
과거를 언급하고 싶지 않으신가요?
I don't want to mention it either
나도 언급하고 싶지 않아
But we can meet again
하지만 우리는 다시 만날 수 있어요
It shows that there is still fate
아직 운명이 남아있다는 걸 보여주네요
Why don't we just meet this time?
우리 이번에만 만나는 게 어때요?
Think of it as a new acquaintance between the two of us
우리 둘 사이의 새로운 지인이라고 생각하세요
what do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
Don't waste any time
시간을 낭비하지 마세요
And me
그리고 나
I already have someone I like
나에겐 이미 좋아하는 사람이 있다
Is it the boy from last time?
저번에 나왔던 그 애야?
no
아니요
My order has been purchased
내 주문이 구매되었습니다
Just stop wasting your time
시간낭비는 그만둬
on me
나에게
you have been abandoned
당신은 버려졌습니다
professor
교수
right
오른쪽
I am the professor
나는 교수이다
Change to Yu Xiaoyue’s sample
Yu Xiaoyue의 샘플로 변경
Is it you too?
당신도 마찬가지인가요?
it's me
나야
This was all arranged by them
이건 다 그 사람들이 정리한 거야
The one who threatens Yu Xiaoyue
우샤오웨를 위협하는 자
Where is Professor Li?
리 교수는 어디에 있나요?
also me
나도
why do you want to hurt her
왜 그녀를 다치게 하려는 거야?
harm her
그녀에게 해를 끼치다
She wants to be an internet celebrity
그녀는 인터넷 연예인이 되고 싶어한다
How can it be that easy?
어떻게 그렇게 쉬울 수 있나요?
Operation and promotion require money
운영과 홍보에는 돈이 필요하다
I'm here to help her make money
나는 그녀가 돈을 벌 수 있도록 돕기 위해 여기 있습니다
I just got into the spy game
방금 스파이 게임에 뛰어들었어요
I want a cup of frozen lemon tea
얼린 레몬차 한잔 마시고 싶어요
OK
좋아요
Complete offline tasks
오프라인 작업 완료
you can make more money
너는 더 많은 돈을 벌 수 있다
to make more money
더 많은 돈을 벌기 위해
I came into contact with offline tasks
오프라인 작업을 접하게 되었습니다
Taken photos of the laboratory
연구실에서 찍은 사진
But when I react
하지만 내가 반응할 때
It's too late
너무 늦었어
Also with my help
그것도 내 도움으로
She became an internet celebrity
그녀는 인터넷 유명인이 되었다
Fire
불
But you want to leave me
하지만 당신은 나를 떠나고 싶어
So you take her
그러니 당신이 그녀를 데려가세요
Also pulled down the water
물도 끌어내렸다
The best way to keep her
그녀를 지키는 가장 좋은 방법
Just destroy her
그냥 그녀를 파괴하세요
Let her become like me
그녀가 나처럼 되도록 해주세요
Boss Zhang gave me this advice
장보스는 나에게 이런 조언을 해주었다
do this
이 작업을 수행
She is because of you
그 사람은 너 때문이야
No access to B13 samples at all
B13 샘플에 전혀 접근할 수 없습니다.
That’s why you harmed Xiaoyue
그래서 당신은 Xiaoyue에게 해를 끼쳤습니다
You two really have the same chemistry.
두 분 정말 케미가 똑같으세요.
Have you met Boss Zhang?
장보스를 만나보셨나요?
We've only met in games
우리는 게임에서만 만났어요
Were there any other contacts?
다른 연락처는 없었나요?
she is cautious
그녀는 조심스럽다
we only had one phone call
우리는 전화 한 통밖에 안 했어
The sound is relatively neutral
소리는 비교적 중립적입니다.
It should be a voice changer
보이스체인저여야지
But sometimes she makes mistakes
하지만 그녀는 가끔 실수를 하기도 해요
What
무엇
I can confirm that Boss Zhang
장보스님이 확인하실 수 있어요
Just in Jinhai
바로 진하이에서
how do you know
어떻게 알아?
Have you heard the bells of Nam Van Harbor?
남반항(Nam Van Harbour)의 종소리를 들어보셨나요?
When I was on the phone with Boss Zhang
장보스와 통화할 때
heard this bell
이 종소리를 들었어
Our campus is right there
우리 캠퍼스가 바로 거기에 있어요
I'm familiar with this bell
나는 이 종소리에 익숙하다.
So Boss Zhang
장보스
Just in Jinhai Nanwan District
진하이 난완 지구에 위치
At least follow me
적어도 날 따라와
She was there during the call
통화 중에 그녀가 거기 있었어
What do you think of this person?
이 사람에 대해 어떻게 생각하세요?
Will I be by your side?
내가 당신 곁에 있어줄까요?
The proprietress of Yuyue Japanese Food Shop
Yuyue 일식점 여주인
Is it related to the spy game?
스파이 게임과 관련이 있나요?
she
그녀
Not possible
불가능
But I'm sure
하지만 난 확신해
person who delivers the sample
샘플을 배달하는 사람
He's the owner of a seafood shop
그는 해산물 가게의 주인이다
i have seen him
나는 그를 본 적이 있어요
The sample is placed
샘플이 놓여있습니다
on his car
그의 차에
I always thought
나는 항상 생각했다
Boss Zhang is only in the game
장보스는 게임에만 참여합니다
avatar
화신
But I didn't expect that she would be in Jinhai
하지만 그녀가 진하이에 있을 줄은 몰랐어요
this for us
이것은 우리를 위한 것입니다
is good news
좋은 소식이다
Qin Chu
진추
I recommend
나는 추천한다
temporarily blocked
일시적으로 차단됨
News of Shi Lei's rescue
시 레이 구출 소식
He knows Han Jie’s identity
그는 한지의 정체를 알고 있다
This is in our hands
이건 우리 손에 달렸어
The most important clue
가장 중요한 단서
I have informed the institute
연구소에 알렸어요
Let them post the obituary
사망 기사를 게시하게 해주세요
Shi Lei was announced dead
Shi Lei가 사망했다고 발표되었습니다.
I hope
나는 희망
I hope this news
이 소식이 왔으면 좋겠습니다
capable of deterring spies
스파이를 저지할 수 있는 능력
doubt
의심
There is also news from the customs
세관에서도 소식이 나오네요
Han Jie recently declared
한지가 최근 선언했다.
a batch of seafood
해산물 한 묶음
To be shipped to Macau
마카오로 보내드립니다
The receiving party is still the same as last time
받는 쪽은 여전히 ​​지난번과 같습니다.
The company that accepted the sample
샘플을 수락한 회사
They have something again
그들에겐 또 뭔가가 있다
About to send it out
발송 예정
Now that Boss Zhang is in control
이제 장보스가 통제권을 쥐고 있으니
The overall situation of Jinhai
진하이의 전반적인 상황
She will definitely contact Han Jie
그녀는 반드시 Han Jie에게 연락할 것이다
Han Jie’s mobile phone and game account
한지에의 휴대폰 및 게임 계정
we keep staring
우리는 계속 쳐다보고 있어
Han Jie has never been online
한지는 온라인에 접속한 적이 없다
It doesn't seem to be related to anything
아무 관련도 없는 것 같은데
suspicious person contact
수상한 사람 연락
but i doubt
하지만 나는 의심한다
He may have more than one cell phone
그는 하나 이상의 휴대폰을 가지고 있을 수도 있습니다
Or maybe he still has
아니면 아직 그 사람이
Other contact information
기타 연락처 정보
So you should pay close attention
그러니 세심한 주의를 기울여야 한다
Han Jie’s movements
한지의 움직임
He could be at any time
그 사람은 언제든지 그럴 수 있어요.
There are new actions
새로운 액션이 있습니다
clear
분명한
How is the situation over there with Huang Zicheng?
저기 황자성 상황은 어떤가요?
Haven't replied to me yet
아직 나에게 답장하지 않았습니다
But I will continue to follow up
하지만 계속 추적하겠습니다.
He cracked the secret agent mission for us
그는 우리를 위해 비밀 요원 임무를 수행했습니다
Still very helpful
여전히 매우 도움이 됩니다
Hello
안녕하세요
Shi Lei is dead
시 레이는 죽었어
sure
확신하는
Obituaries issued by the institute
연구소에서 발행한 사망 기사
Good to know
알아 둘만 한
I am at home
나는 집에 있다
And you
당신은요
correct
옳은
Do me a favor tomorrow
내일 부탁 좀 해주세요
no problem
괜찮아요
Where is this yacht club?
이 요트 클럽은 어디에 있나요?
It’s the whole Jinhai
진하이 전체에요
The largest yacht club
가장 큰 요트 클럽
Mr. Fang has arrived
팡 씨가 도착했어요
Let me introduce to you
당신에게 소개하겠습니다
Fang Lu
팡 루
Come
오다
Let me introduce
소개하겠습니다
This is Mr. Fang
팡씨입니다
He is currently in Jinhai
그는 현재 진하이에 있다
Preparing to build a private art museum
사립 미술관 건립 준비
Where are these two?
이 둘은 어디에 있나요?
is the odyssey art foundation
오디세이 아트 파운데이션입니다
Overseas development manager
해외개발부장
Good morning sir
좋은 아침입니다 선생님
everything fine
다 괜찮아
everything is fine
모든 게 괜찮아
That's good
좋아요
Please entertain me
저를 즐겁게 해주세요
I'll go to the kitchen and have a look
주방에 가서 살펴볼게요
good
좋은
please
제발
Thanks
감사해요
Do you want to try it?
시도해 보시겠습니까?
How about it
어때요?
marvelous
기이
correct
옳은
How is the seafood I ordered?
내가 주문한 해산물은 어떤가요?
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
what you want
당신이 원하는 것
I picked them all myself
내가 다 직접 골랐어
Thanks
감사해요
between us
우리 사이
Don't be so polite
너무 예의바르게 굴지 마
Thanks for your hard work, Boss Han cooked the food himself.
노고에 감사드리며, 한 사장님께서 직접 음식을 요리해 주셨습니다.
Always borrow Mr. Chen’s yacht
항상 첸 선생님의 요트를 빌려주세요
Go fishing
낚시를
Is it appropriate to do some work?
어떤 일을 하는 것이 적절한가요?
Mr. Han just went fishing
한씨는 방금 낚시하러 갔어요
Do you want to try it?
시도해 보시겠습니까?
OK
좋아요
have a taste
맛 좀 봐
How about it
어때요?
It melts in your mouth
입에서 녹는다
Thanks to Brother Han
한 형제님 덕분에
How can I have such a good taste?
어쩜 이렇게 맛이 좋을 수가 있지?
Him
그를
But tuna enthusiast
하지만 참치 매니아
I went abroad to study
나는 유학을 갔다
This split fish for him
그를 위한 이 쪼개진 물고기
Just a kind of enjoyment
그냥 일종의 즐거움
Then my brother and I are pretty much the same
그럼 내 동생과 나는 거의 똑같아
the only difference
유일한 차이점
I am the one who eats fish
나는 생선을 먹는 사람이다
as a kind of enjoyment
일종의 즐거움으로
Really good
정말 좋다
How was the conversation above?
위의 대화는 어땠나요?
I feel very good
기분이 좋아
It's almost time for us to set sail.
이제 항해를 시작할 시간이 거의 다 왔습니다.
Okay, I'll do it right away
알았어, 바로 해볼게
Good to go
가도 좋아요
Walk
걷다
what did you eat
무엇을 먹었나요?
It's all fine
다 괜찮아
Do you think this one is okay?
이거 괜찮은 것 같아?
Then sit down
그럼 앉으세요
If you are allergic, why don't you feed the cat?
알레르기가 있다면 고양이에게 먹이를 주는 게 어때요?
The more dangerous things are
더 위험한 일은
The more people want to get closer
더 가까이 다가가고 싶어하는 사람들이 많아질수록
That's why we
그렇기 때문에 우리는
Meet in the agent game
에이전트 게임에서 만나보세요
Don’t you regret it?
후회하지 않나요?
No regrets
후회 없다
There is no point in regretting
후회해도 소용없어
the most important
가장 중요한
is to solve the problem
문제를 해결하는 것이다
How to solve it
해결 방법
The problem is not as serious as you think
문제는 생각보다 심각하지 않습니다
I've already asked
나는 이미 물었습니다.
without knowing it
그것을 모르고
make mistakes
실수하다
There will be no heavy sentence
무거운 형벌은 없을 것
But no
하지만
Help from both of us
우리 둘 모두의 도움
those people behind
뒤에 있는 사람들
Can't get anything either
아무것도 얻을 수 없습니다
And last night
그리고 어젯밤
I've checked
나는 확인했다
This is our situation
이것이 우리의 상황이다
Even if it is a joint crime
공동범죄라 하더라도
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
Look
바라보다
People who enter Dr. Feng’s room
펑 박사의 방에 들어가는 사람들
It's me
나야
The person who plugs the USB flash drive into the computer
USB 플래시 드라이브를 컴퓨터에 연결하는 사람
also me
나도
I am also the accomplice
나도 공범이다
I did it all by myself
나 혼자 다 해냈어
You are just playing games
넌 그냥 게임을 하고 있는 거야
What am I going in for?
나는 무엇을 위해 들어가고 있습니까?
You don't know either
너도 모르지
But I know
하지만 난 알아
Then forget about before
그럼 아까 일은 잊어버려
Our conversation
우리의 대화
stop talking
그만 얘기해
Already know about the spy mission
스파이 임무에 대해 이미 알고 있습니다.
Such nonsense
이런 말도 안되는 소리
this is for you
이건 널위한거야
what do you mean
무슨 뜻이에요
You're not worried
당신은 걱정하지 않습니다
Game binding credit card
게임 바인딩 신용카드
Will the credit be deducted?
크레딧이 차감되나요?
Here is one hundred thousand dollars
여기 10만 달러가 있어요
This is me
이게 나야
I usually don’t have any savings.
나는 보통 저축한 돈이 전혀 없다.
all of a sudden
갑자기
I can only get so much
너무 많이 얻을 수 밖에 없어
It was Jiang Xiaohua who helped me
나를 도와준 사람은 장샤오화였다.
But
하지만
You listen to me first
당신이 먼저 내 말을 들어요
I don't know
모르겠습니다
How much money is tied to your credit card?
귀하의 신용카드에 얼마나 많은 금액이 연결되어 있습니까?
Where is the money?
돈은 어디에 있습니까?
It may not be enough
충분하지 않을 수도 있습니다
But your ability and academic qualifications
하지만 당신의 능력과 학력은
Not bad at all
나쁘지 않아
Not playing games
게임을 하지 않음
You can definitely make money
넌 분명 돈을 벌 수 있을 거야
so
그래서
can you exit the game
게임 종료할 수 있어?
I can't accept it
나는 그것을 받아들일 수 없다
why
왜
no reason
이유없이
I can't take your money
나는 당신의 돈을 가져갈 수 없습니다
Just think I borrowed it from you
그냥 내가 너한테 빌린 것 같아
When will you have money?
언제 돈이 생기나요?
When will you pay me back?
언제 갚으시겠어요?
Isn’t it over?
끝나지 않았나요?
I just hope you can understand
나는 단지 당신이 이해할 수 있기를 바랍니다
The spy's grip
스파이의 손아귀
Not a threat to you
당신에게 위협이 되지 않습니다
And money can solve things
그리고 돈이 문제를 해결할 수 있어요
It's not a big trouble
큰 문제는 아니죠
But this game
하지만 이 게임은
You must not play anymore
더 이상 놀면 안 돼
If you keep playing
계속 플레이하다보면
My whole life is ruined
내 인생 전체가 망가졌어
But in your case
하지만 당신의 경우에는
Not much better than me
나보다 별로 낫지 않아
Didn’t you also bind the card?
카드도 묶지 않았나요?
Don't worry about me
내 걱정은 하지 마세요
I have a way
나에겐 방법이 있다
any solution
어떤 솔루션이라도
Eat old age
노년을 먹어라
good
좋은
I promise you
약속 할게
exit the game
게임 종료
Very good
매우 좋은
Then give your bank card
그럼 은행 카드를 줘
you wait later
나중에 기다려
Don't be so naive
너무 순진하게 굴지 마세요
In that game
그 게임에서는
Which offline player is innocent?
어떤 오프라인 플레이어가 결백합니까?
Including your partner
파트너 포함
no
아니요
You just said it casually
그냥 아무렇지도 않게 말했잖아
I still really think there is something wrong with Yao Yao
나는 아직도 야오야오에게 뭔가 문제가 있다고 생각한다.
Did you persuade her to quit the game?
게임을 그만두도록 설득했나요?
I guess she won't withdraw
내 생각엔 그 사람은 물러나지 않을 것 같아
This is an IOU
차용증입니다
I owe you the money
나는 당신에게 돈을 빚지고 있어요
OK
좋아요
The boss orders
사장님이 주문하시더라구요
Two bottles of beer
맥주 두 병
coming
오는
let's celebrate
축하하자
What's there to celebrate?
축하할 일이 뭐 있나요?
I'm really afraid that you will reject me
당신이 나를 거부할까 봐 정말 두려워요
If she really has a problem
그녀에게 정말 문제가 있다면
She should always be
그녀는 항상 있어야합니다
Just keep playing, right?
그냥 계속 놀아요, 그렇죠?
you don't know very well
당신은 잘 몰라요
Is this the secret agent world?
여기가 비밀요원의 세계인가요?
people there
거기 사람들
All have different faces
다들 얼굴이 다르네
Not so easy to distinguish
구별하기가 쉽지 않네요
Who is the big bad wolf and who is the little white rabbit?
크고 나쁜 늑대는 누구이고, 작은 흰 토끼는 누구인가요?
You're not talking about those people
당신은 그 사람들에 대해 말하는 것이 아닙니다
Are they all here for you?
그 사람들이 모두 당신을 위해 여기 있나요?
What if they come to you again?
그들이 당신에게 다시 오면 어떻게 되나요?
do not worry about me
나에 대해 걱정하지 마세요
I can deal with them
나는 그들을 상대할 수 있다
any solution
어떤 솔루션이라도
them
그들을
It must be what happened before
이전에 일어난 일임에 틀림없어
threaten me
나를 위협하다
It's really not possible
정말 불가능해요
I reported this to my boss
나는 이 사실을 상사에게 보고했다.
Anyway, she was the one responsible for both of us.
어쨌든 그녀는 우리 둘 모두의 책임을 맡은 사람이었습니다.
I can't find Boss Zhang
장보스를 찾을 수 없어요
Then the National Security Bureau will definitely find her.
그러면 국가안전보위부가 반드시 그녀를 찾아낼 것이다.
When the time comes
때가되면
I can still be considered guilty and meritorious.
나는 여전히 유죄이고 가치 있는 사람으로 간주될 수 있습니다.
Definitely get a lighter punishment
반드시 가벼운 처벌을 받아라
Come
오다
cheers
건배
end our gaming career
게임 인생을 끝내다
You won't regret it, will you?
후회하지 않을 거예요, 그렇죠?
I'll log it off now
이제 로그오프하겠습니다
Won't you come together?
같이 가지 않을래?
Together
함께
The professor is out of control
교수가 통제불능이네
It's no shame to get rid of it
없애는 건 부끄러운 일이 아니다
At least you can use him
적어도 당신은 그를 사용할 수 있습니다
To draw the attention of Guoan
궈안의 관심을 끌기 위해
Keep our more important people
더 중요한 사람들을 지켜주세요
He is still sleeping
그 사람 아직도 자고 있어요
when necessary
필요할 땐
i will wake him up
내가 그를 깨울게요
Your other Kingsman
또 다른 킹스맨
how's it going
어떻게되고 있습니까
Huang Zicheng and Yao Yao
황쯔쳉(Huang Zicheng)과 야오야오(Yao Yao)
Log out of the game
게임에서 로그아웃하세요
Don't worry
괜찮아요
I will find a way
나는 방법을 찾을 것이다
Hello
안녕하세요
Zicheng
자성
Your father fainted
네 아버지는 기절하셨어
I'll take him to the hospital now
지금 병원에 데려갈게요
What's up with him
그 사람 무슨 일이야?
The situation is not clear yet
아직 상황은 명확하지 않습니다
You'd better come here quickly
빨리 여기로 오는 게 좋을 거야
I am coming over now
나 지금 오고 있어
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
Something happened to my dad
아버지에게 무슨 일이 일어났어요
Then I'll go with you
그럼 나도 같이 갈게
No big problem
큰 문제는 없습니다
Have a good rest
편안히 휴식을 취하다
thank you doctor
고마워요 의사
doctor
의사
How is my dad doing?
우리 아빠는 어떻게 지내세요?
High blood pressure caused by excessive fatigue
과도한 피로로 인한 고혈압
The condition is now under control
현재 상태는 통제되고 있습니다
That
저것
Is the situation serious?
상황이 심각한가요?
Not serious
진지하지 않다
But in the future
하지만 앞으로는
Be sure to take a rest
꼭 쉬세요
Don't let him get emotional
그 사람이 감정적으로 반응하도록 두지 마세요.
Don’t be too nervous and get tired
너무 긴장하고 지치지 마세요
Okay, I will supervise him
알았어, 내가 감독할게
Observe for two days
이틀간 관찰해보세요
no problem
괜찮아요
You can be discharged from the hospital
병원에서 퇴원할 수 있습니다.
Thank you thank you doctor
감사합니다 박사님 감사합니다
This matter
이 문제
I also have a responsibility
나에게도 책임이 있다
What’s your work schedule these days?
요즘 근무 일정은 어떻게 되나요?
relatively tight
상대적으로 꽉
last night
지난 밤
I stayed up all night
나는 밤새도록 깨어 있었다
I just forgot to look
나는 단지 보는 것을 잊었다
His physical condition is gone
그의 신체 상태가 사라졌습니다
Don't blame yourself too much
너무 자신을 비난하지 마세요
No one can control him
누구도 그를 통제할 수 없어
OK
좋아요
Then I'll go get Mr. Huang's medicine first.
그럼 먼저 황 선생님의 약을 사러 가겠습니다.
I'm leaving
나는 떠난다
Okay, don't worry anymore
알았어, 더 이상 걱정하지 마
The doctor also said it's nothing serious
의사도 심각한 것은 아니라고 하더군요
That
저것
Come in and stay with your uncle.
들어와서 삼촌과 함께 지내세요.
I'll leave first
내가 먼저 떠날게
thank you
감사합니다
Gone
다 쓴
Still pretending
아직도 그런 척하고 있어
Where am I?
내가 어디 있지?
I said you are so old
나는 당신이 너무 늙었다고 말했어요
Why else are you staying up late?
또 왜 늦게까지 안 자요?
I thought I was young
난 내가 어리다고 생각했는데
Is it okay now?
이제 괜찮아요?
The doctor told you to be hospitalized
의사가 입원하라고 하더군요
have a good rest
편안히 휴식을 취하다
The doctor just said
의사가 방금 말했어요
I'm fine
잘 지내요
Didn't you just wake up?
방금 일어난 거 아니었어?
What did the doctor say?
의사가 뭐라고 했습니까?
You all know
다들 아시죠
I'm telling you, you
내가 말하잖아, 너
Just take this opportunity
이번 기회에 그냥 가져가세요
give me good
나에게 좋은 것을 줘
Get a general check-up
종합검진을 받아보세요
Did you hear that?
그거 들었어?
There is another meeting on the weekend
주말에 또 모임이 있어요
Let's talk about it when I come back
내가 돌아오면 얘기하자
Just now
방금
Who is that girl?
그 소녀는 누구입니까?
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
The eyes are pretty good
눈이 참 좋은데
when i
내가 언제
Don't let your guard down
경계심을 늦추지 마세요
A friend of mine
내 친구
How did we know each other?
우리는 어떻게 서로를 알았나요?
We met while playing games
게임하다가 만났어요
I see
알겠어요
That's the one
그게 바로 그거야
An unreliable game
신뢰할 수 없는 게임
I said can you have a good rest?
내가 말했잖아, 푹 쉬어도 돼?
Stop worrying about me every day
매일 내 걱정 그만해
You run around every day
넌 매일 뛰어다녀
Not even a serious job
진지한 직업도 아니고
Can I not worry?
걱정하지 않아도 될까요?
How old are you?
몇 살이에요?
Can you put that game away?
그 게임을 치워줄 수 있나요?
That game
그 게임
I'm really tired of playing
놀다가 진짜 지쳤어
I'm going to play a new one now
이제 새로운 게임을 하려고 해요
Challenge upgrades are more exciting
챌린지 업그레이드가 더욱 흥미진진해졌습니다.
do you think
당신은 생각합니까
I've lived too long
너무 오래 살았어
Can you learn from your brother?
형에게서 배울 수 있나요?
I just plan to be like him
나도 그 사람처럼 될 생각이야
Let's go together
같이 가자
Do a big job
큰일을 해라
What's the meaning
무슨 뜻인가요?
Just kidding you
농담이에요
You little bastard
이 작은 놈아
Are you kidding me?
농담하는 거야?
I have informed
나는 알렸다
Gao Tianyang is here
Gao Tianyang이 여기에 있습니다
when
언제
I'll probably be there soon.
아마 곧 도착할 것 같아요.
Just wait to be scolded.
꾸짖을 때까지 기다리십시오.
I suddenly feel sleepy
갑자기 졸려요
I want to sleep for a while
잠시 자고 싶어
Don't let him come
그 사람이 오지 못하게 하세요
I have nothing to do
나는 할 일이 없다
Let Xiao Liu
샤오류를 보자
Sent me back
나를 돌려보냈다
You should have a good rest.
당신은 좋은 휴식을 취해야합니다.
Okay, okay, okay
알았어 알았어 알았어
Let's go, let's go
가자, 가자
How about it
어때요?
He is still me
그 사람은 아직도 나야
he
그
Nothing's wrong with him
그 사람에겐 아무 문제 없어
I heard you are coming
당신이 온다는 소식을 들었어요
Go to sleep quickly
빨리 자러 가세요
Let him have a good rest
그 사람이 잘 쉬게 해주세요
don't bother him
그 사람을 괴롭히지 마세요
go out and chat
나가서 얘기 좀 해
Let's go
갑시다
elder brother
형
You know my childhood dream
내 어린 시절 꿈을 알잖아
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
what
무엇
Superman
슈퍼맨
save the earth
지구를 구해라
still
아직
Boss
사장
Dominate the world
세계를 지배하세요
so
그래서
I've thought about it
생각해 봤는데
I have to help you
나는 당신을 도와야합니다
Kill them
그들을 죽여
Give the game a pure land
게임에 순수한 땅을 주세요
Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉
This is not a joke
이건 농담이 아니야
I mean everything I said
내가 말한 모든 것을 의미합니다.
you
너
you know what you have to face
당신은 당신이 직면해야 할 일을 알고
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Not in your game
당신의 게임에는 없습니다
What villain?
무슨 악당?
is a real spy
진짜 스파이야
I know
알아요
They dragged me into the water
그들은 나를 물속으로 끌고 갔다
Is it just for Lao Huang?
라오황만을 위한 것인가?
Then I have to go even more
그럼 더 가봐야지
If I don't go
내가 가지 않으면
They also have to replace them with someone else
또한 다른 사람으로 교체해야 합니다.
Lao Huang's physical condition
라오황의 컨디션
you saw it too
너도 봤지
I'll get hurt by mistake again.
실수로 또 다치겠다.
In this case
이 경우
Then I have to go even more
그럼 더 가봐야지
But
하지만
Where am I now?
나는 지금 어디에 있습니까?
Encountered a little trouble
약간의 문제가 발생했습니다.
that is
그건
My game account has been canceled
내 게임 계정이 취소되었습니다
Do you think they can still find me?
그 사람들이 아직도 날 찾을 수 있을 것 같아?
Logged out
로그아웃됨
Not just to test Yao Yao
야오야오를 테스트하는 것뿐만 아니라
Advise her to quit the game
그녀에게 게임을 그만두라고 조언하세요
Unexpectedly, she logged out
의외로 로그아웃됐네요
Then I do it for
그럼 내가 할게
Do not arouse her suspicion
그녀의 의심을 일으키지 마십시오
I can only log out as well.
로그아웃만 가능해요.
You have to admit it this time
이번엔 인정해야 해
Did you make a mistake in your judgment?
판단에 착오가 있었나요?
Don’t you talk about Yao Yao
야오야오에 대해 얘기하지 마세요
Won't you quit the game?
게임 그만 두지 않을래?
Who told you to act without permission?
누가 허락 없이 행동하라고 했나요?
I said you are still in the game
내가 말했잖아 넌 아직 게임 중이잖아
What about you, Kingsman?
킹스맨 당신은 어떻습니까?
madness
광기
Not that me
나 말고
You just can't do it at all
넌 전혀 할 수 없어
real world agents
실제 에이전트
You don't know at all
당신은 전혀 모른다
What are you facing?
당신은 무엇에 직면하고 있습니까?
What is it
그것은 무엇입니까?
Your little move
당신의 작은 움직임
you can cause
당신은 일으킬 수 있습니다
All plans shattered
모든 계획이 망가졌어
The anti-Japanese struggle is so cruel
항일투쟁은 참 잔혹하다
I can't tolerate any of your worries
난 너의 어떤 걱정도 용납할 수 없어
I can't tolerate those of yours either
나도 너의 그런 것들은 용납할 수 없어
childish emotions
유치한 감정
no
아니요
Then tell me
그럼 말 해주세요
How can I be one
내가 어떻게 하나가 될 수 있나요?
qualified agent
자격을 갖춘 대리인
Just like you
당신처럼
you knew it early
넌 일찍 알았지
I'm playing that game
나 그 게임 하고 있어
You know that game is dangerous
게임이 위험한 거 아시죠?
but didn't tell me
하지만 나한테는 말하지 않았어
Even if you are my brother
네가 내 동생이라 해도
yes
예
If that's the case
그렇다면
You are really one
당신은 정말 하나입니다
qualified agent
자격을 갖춘 대리인
sorry
죄송합니다
i can never do it
난 절대 할 수 없어
people like you
당신 같은 사람들
but i tell you
하지만 난 너에게 말해
Just wait and see
두고 봐
If I become an agent
내가 대리인이 된다면
Definitely better than you
확실히 너보다 나은데
Huang Zicheng asked Yao Yao
황쯔쳉이 야오야오에게 물었다.
Canceled account
해지된 계정
He went to test Yao Yao
그는 야오야오를 시험하러 갔다
smart-aleck
스마트 알렉
It's really wrong to make decisions without permission
허락 없이 결정을 내리는 것은 정말 잘못된 일입니다
But he has a very positive attitude
하지만 그 사람은 매우 긍정적인 태도를 가지고 있어요.
There is no point in being active.
적극적으로 활동하는 것은 의미가 없습니다.
I don't need him to be active
그 사람이 적극적으로 활동할 필요는 없어
I grew up with him
나는 그와 함께 자랐다
I can't hold back his character.
나는 그의 성격을 참을 수 없다.
You said it sounds nice
좋은 것 같다고 하셨어요
Passion and friendship
열정과 우정
You need to be involved in the anti-Japanese struggle
항일투쟁에 참여해야 합니다
Just this kind of behavior
딱 이런 행동이네
You can die at any time
넌 언제든지 죽을 수 있어
So you start from the beginning
그러니까 처음부터 시작하는 거야
I didn't want him to get involved
나는 그 사람이 관여하는 것을 원하지 않았다
right
오른쪽
Things pushed him to
상황이 그를 밀어붙였다
This position is up
이 위치는 위
He must bear it
그 사람이 견뎌내야 해
This responsibility
이 책임
But he hasn't realized it yet
하지만 그 사람은 아직 그걸 깨닫지 못했어
danger of things
사물의 위험
He met Boss Zhang
그는 장 상사를 만났다
It’s all in the game
모든 것이 게임에 담겨 있습니다
on the Internet
인터넷에서
He doesn't know at all
그 사람은 전혀 몰라요
this fight
이 싸움
real dangers faced
직면한 실제 위험
But he is very smart
하지만 그 사람은 아주 똑똑해요
He knows we are protecting him
그는 우리가 그를 보호하고 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다
So he is not afraid at all
그래서 그는 전혀 두려워하지 않습니다
You can do it
할 수 있어요
I know him better than you
나는 당신보다 그 사람을 더 잘 압니다.
He's just a conceited agent.
그는 단지 자만하는 요원일 뿐입니다.
He simply can't do it
그 사람은 도저히 할 수가 없어
The task we gave him
우리가 그에게 준 임무
I'll help you train him
내가 그를 훈련시키는 것을 도와줄게
I'm not as pessimistic as you
나는 너만큼 비관적이지 않아
He can only see a corner
그 사람은 한쪽 구석만 볼 수 있어
And we can see it all
그리고 우리는 그 모든 것을 볼 수 있어요
I have confidence in him
나는 그 사람을 신뢰한다
Believe me
나를 믿어
Do you still like to play this?
아직도 이 게임을 좋아하시나요?
I want to fight now
나는 지금 싸우고 싶다
Come
오다
how do you feel
기분이 어때?
Dissatisfied
불만족
I wasn't ready just now
지금은 준비가 안 됐어요
Come again
다시 오세요
So how do you feel now?
그럼 지금 기분이 어떤가요?
Impressed
깊은 인상
have a drink together
같이 한잔하다
good
좋은
This place is really nice
이 곳은 정말 좋아요
It must be extremely difficult to make an appointment
약속잡기가 엄청 힘들텐데
Nothing I choose is wrong
내가 선택한 건 아무것도 틀리지 않아
I'll hang out with you after it's settled
일이 해결된 후에 같이 놀게요
your martini
네 마티니
your mojito
너의 모히토
Thanks
감사해요
alcohol free
무알콜
How do you know I like to drink this?
내가 이거 마시는 걸 좋아하는 줄 어떻게 알았어?
Your brother said that
네 형이 그러더라고.
My brother goes back
형은 돌아간다
I won't tell you anymore
더 이상 말하지 않겠습니다
A lot of bad things about me, right?
나에 대해 나쁜 점이 많죠?
All good words
다 좋은 말
Hot-blooded boy
열혈소년
It doesn't sound like it
그런 것 같지 않은데
You don't need to worry about him
그 사람에 대해 걱정할 필요가 없습니다
I think you did a very good job
내 생각엔 당신이 아주 좋은 일을 했다고 생각해요
You really think so
정말 그렇게 생각하니
Positive attitude towards work
일에 대한 긍정적인 태도
Be affectionate and loyal to friends
친구에게 다정하고 충성심을 가지세요
Still you understand me
그래도 넌 날 이해해
If I had known earlier, I would have talked to you directly.
미리 알았더라면 직접 얘기를 했을 텐데.
Isn’t it over?
끝나지 않았나요?
But there is one thing
그런데 한 가지가 있어요
Since you agreed to cooperate with us
당신이 우리와 협력하기로 동의했기 때문에
Discipline comes first
규율이 우선이다
Our work
우리의 일
It’s different from playing games with you
너랑 게임하는거랑은 달라
No chance to do it again
다시는 할 기회가 없어
any move
어떤 계획이든
All must be discussed
모두 논의해야 함
no one
아무도
Can be a lone hero
고독한 영웅이 될 수 있다
Then can I discuss it with you directly?
그럼 제가 직접 의논해도 될까요?
i think you speak
내 생각엔 당신이 말하는 것 같아요
It's more palatable than him
그 사람보다 더 맛있어
Okay
좋아요
Any instructions received in the future
앞으로 받을 모든 지시
Contact me as soon as possible
가능한 한 빨리 연락주세요
sure
확신하는
but other things
하지만 다른 것들은
No need to report it, right?
신고할 필요는 없겠죠?
Things other than work
일 이외의 것
Of course not
당연히 아니지
For example, you have been secretly paying attention to
예를 들어, 당신은 비밀리에 주의를 기울여 왔습니다.
Those two pretty girls behind me
내 뒤에 있는 예쁜 여자 두 명
Okay, Sister Xi
알았어, 시 언니
Who doesn’t like to see beautiful women?
아름다운 여성을 보고 싶지 않은 사람이 어디 있겠습니까?
You
너
Nothing like Guoan's
Guoan과 같은 것은 없습니다
What is the national security like?
국가 안보는 어떤가요?
National security
국가 안보
I think it should be
내 생각엔 그래야 한다고 생각해
Like Gao Tianyang
가오텐양처럼
When you talk to me
당신이 나에게 말할 때
Not an underground garage
지하주차장이 아닌
It's a place for senior citizens to hang out
어르신들이 쉬어갈 수 있는 공간이에요
He can compare with me
그 사람은 나와 비교될 수 ​​있어
That's far from it
그거랑은 거리가 멀다
Don't understand life
인생을 이해하지 못한다
It's quite tiring to work with him, right?
그 사람이랑 같이 일하는 건 꽤 피곤한 일이잖아요?
I can't help myself
나는 나 자신을 도울 수 없다
Too
도
You said I have such a brother
나한테 그런 동생이 있다고 했잖아
But he is this person
그런데 그 사람이 바로 이 사람이에요
Usually pretty good
평소엔 꽤 괜찮았는데
As soon as I start working
일 시작하자마자
It's like a different person
딴사람같네
Because he is worried about you
그 사람이 당신을 걱정하고 있으니까요
you haven't seen it yet
넌 아직 못 봤잖아
The cruelty of the struggle
투쟁의 잔인함
You made a wrong move
당신은 잘못된 행동을 했습니다
Not just a total loss
단순한 손실이 아닌
even sacrifice
심지어 희생한다
He is really worried about you
그 사람은 정말 당신을 걱정하고 있어요
when i go out
내가 나갈 때
He also warned me
그 사람도 나한테 경고했어
Really
정말
certainly
틀림없이
he knows
그는 알고있다
After you are a gamer
게이머가 된 후
Although he didn't say
비록 그가 말하지는 않았지만
but i can feel it
하지만 난 느낄 수 있어
He believes in you
그 사람은 당신을 믿습니다
Even want to stop you
막고 싶어도
End Game
최종 단계
But I rejected it
그런데 거절했어요
why
왜
we need you to cooperate with us
우리는 당신이 우리와 협력해야
we believe you
우리는 당신을 믿습니다
Have the brains to deal with them
그것들을 다룰 수 있는 두뇌를 가지고 있어
If it were my brother
만약 내 동생이었다면
It would be nice if you could say these things to me
나한테 이런 말을 해주면 좋을 텐데.
This person
이 사람
All the words are hidden in the stomach
모든 말은 뱃속에 숨겨져 있다
Even if it's bad, he won't say anything.
나쁘더라도 아무 말도하지 않을 것입니다.
Very annoying
매우 짜증나
That's how virtuous he is
그 사람은 그만큼 덕이 있는 사람이야
I secretly forgive him
나는 그를 몰래 용서한다
several times
여러번
That's right
좋아요
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
How do you know my brother so well?
어떻게 내 동생을 그렇게 잘 알아요?
We are partners
우리는 파트너입니다
Just a partner
그냥 파트너
Right
오른쪽
Just like him
그 사람처럼
You must not like it
좋아하지 않으면 안 돼
correct
옳은
You and Yao Yao
당신과 야오야오
Let’s quit the game together, right?
같이 게임 그만하자, 응?
yes
예
but
하지만
I could only do this at that time
그땐 이것밖에 할 수 없었어
well-done
잘하셨어요
Hide identity
신원 숨기기
is the most important thing to you
당신에게 가장 중요한 것은
Catching spies is our business
간첩을 잡는 것이 우리의 일이다
Remember?
기억하다?
remember
기억하다
Since they are thinking carefully
신중하게 생각하고 있기 때문에
Want to drag you into the water
널 물속으로 끌고 가고 싶어
I will definitely come to you again
나는 반드시 다시 당신에게 올 것이다
Next
다음
What should you do?
당신은 무엇을 해야 합니까?
live your life well
인생을 잘 살아라
But you must be mentally prepared
하지만 정신적으로 준비가 되어 있어야 해요
if they come to you again
그 사람들이 또 너한테 오면
Never act rashly
절대로 함부로 행동하지 마세요
I'll notify you when I have the opportunity
기회되면 알려드릴게요
1327099103
1327099103
My memory is pretty good
내 기억력은 꽤 좋은 편이야
Worthy of being a level 28 player
레벨 28 플레이어가 될 자격이 있습니다
You also play agent missions
에이전트 임무도 수행합니다.
My level is not higher than yours
내 레벨은 너보다 높지 않아
Mr. Dana Wong
다나 웡 씨
Then before we two
그럼 우리 둘이 전에
Have you seen it in the game?
게임에서 본 적 있나요?
I know you
나는 당신을 알고
but you don't know me
하지만 당신은 나를 몰라요
I see
알겠어요
You were in the game before
당신은 이전에 게임에 참여했습니다
Start investigating me
나에 대한 조사를 시작해 보세요
Then am I
그렇다면 나는?
When will it be online?
온라인은 언제 되나요?
You all know
다들 아시죠